bloggeraz.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | My PC Note

## The Privacy of Our Visitors is Important to myPCnote.

At **myPCnote.com** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit **myPCnote.com** , and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a [popup](http://mypcnote.com/PopupDomination) once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on **myPCnote.com** to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

## DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ( “interest based targeting” ). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Canada, you may see Canada hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as [Norton](http://mypcnote.com/topnortonproducts) Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## Email Addresses

When you make a comment or contact **myPCnote** using the contact page your email id is required. Please be assured that your email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever.

## Comments Policy

The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectional and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster will be banned! Comments made for sole purpose of getting backlinks or advertizing your/any product will not be accepted. Link to third party website will require moderation and we reserve the rights to edit/delete such links. Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately. **myPCnote** may take action against such spammers.

## Amazon Affiliate

**myPCnote.com** is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

## Contents

**myPCnote.com** respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please [email to us](http://mypcnote.com/contact/) and we will remove the content immediately.
